hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
jeremyarkowski if we haven't met yet I
help coaches trainers and mentors scale
their businesses to seven and eight
figures and I want to help you break
past what's stopping you from getting
the kind of sales leads customers and
clients that you want in your business
if you don't have leads coming in every
single day every single week you don't
have a business and that's what I help
people with is how to grow their
business how to get more clients and how
to have more impact how to make six and
seven figures real money in their
business what we're going to talk about
is virtual events virtual events right
now is the number one way to grow your
coaching business is the number one way
to grow your course business because
they give you an opportunity to connect
with prospects to demonstrate what you
do and to grow your email list all at
the same time they work better than a
freebie they work better than a free
ebook they work better than a mini
master class because your connect thing
live with people you're bringing people
into a virtual space with you live to
where you can connect with them people
that are brand new people that you've
never talked to or maybe people that you
have worked with before to demonstrate
your value to show them what it's like
to work with you and why they should
hire you and what this does is this
allows you to connect with potential
prospects what do you do during one of
these virtual events well you deliver
value you actually give people value and
and it's not about like holding back a
lot you actually want to give away your
very best content for free in a virtual
event you want to give away your very
best transformational piece of
information that's going to help people
now how do you know what that actually
is well you got to actually be coaching
people and you got to actually actively
be working with people if you're not
working with people if you're not
coaching anybody you need to start doing
that virtual events is a great way to
test this out because you're able to
pull people into a space bring them into
like a Facebook group for a couple of
days or for a couple of hours on one day
and you can communicate and connect and
talk with them and you help bring a
result to their life and so you start
with what is the problem that you solve
in your event what is the problem that
the prospect has what is the solution
that they're going to get out of it and
then at the end of your event
you make a call to action and you tell
people to sign up for something and by
doing this you're able to nurture trust
show people what it's like to work with
you be able to demonstrate your value
and connect with them on a level that
they will buy from you this is how our
clients are making seven figures right
now this is how we're making multiple
six figures in our business right now
this is how we're helping a number of my
coaching clients go from zero to six
figures in less than one month is with
virtual events
all other types of lead generation ways
of growing and coaching in the course
business
are a lot slower than this
so that's why we're recommending
everybody do virtual events that's why
we're recommending everybody start to do
virtual events it's like you've never
done an event before it's as simple as
this find
a day on your calendar to do a one day
event pick a day
[Music]
um and and a lot of people unfortunately
usually pick a day that's way too soon
and then they give too much pressure on
themselves here's what I would recommend
pick a day that's like
three weeks out that way you give
yourself the next week to come up with
what your topic of your event is
you give yourself the week after to
build out your landing page and your
autoresponders and then you promote it
for a week okay you want to promote your
virtual event for at least a week to
people if you don't people don't have
enough time to plan to actually show up
live with you and then what you're going
to do is you're going to bring value to
those people you're going to connect
with them and that's where the practice
of you doing that you're going to get
better at connecting with people on
camera selling to them on camera a lot
of people are not very good at
connecting on camera they're not good
communicators they they want to focus so
much on how can I have impact on people
how can I connect how can I coach people
and yet they've never even done it
before and so a virtual event is a great
way to grow in your skill set of
coaching to connect with people and to
grow your email list so when people sign
up for your event they're going to start
by giving you their name and email
address
now those people are on your email list
and here's the truth only about three to
five percent of anybody who comes on
your email list is going to actually buy
anything from you that's normal those
numbers are normal
meaning one in every 20 person who signs
up might spend any money with you one in
every
30 people might spend any money with you
that's normal those are normal numbers
I see way too often beginners get really
bent out of shape because oh I only got
five people that signed up well if you
spent 500 and you made five thousand
like my client Angie that's a profit
that's good that's a great result
and so celebrate the wins that you have
listen in my book if you're running a
virtual event and you break even on your
virtual event cost
you've done a win because you have
increased your email list you have
connected with people and it will
compound over time by you doing that and
the more you do this the more that you
have offers that you put out there that
you sell to people and what we're
recommending is that you sell your
courses and coaching for at least 997
dollars way too many coaches and course
creators are selling stuff for way too
cheap and they can't make enough money
off of their virtual events
and so you want to sell for 997 dollars
something that you're going to offer
people and so you got to identify this
is where what I help people do in my
client growth accelerator is we dial in
and work with you on what's your copy is
your ads dialed in is your funnels
working is it connecting with people is
it connecting the dots is it connecting
emotionally with what the prospect needs
because here's the thing you can put a
virtual event out there and and if it's
not going to connect with anybody you're
gonna spend a whole lot of money on
Advertising you're going to lose a lot
of money because nobody's actually going
to sign up for it that's going to be a
Target Prospect if you go too broad
nobody's going to purchase from you
either because they don't really want
what you're throwing down they don't
really have a desire for the thing that
you're trying to sell them and so you
got to be testing different forms of
messaging we use tools like
answerthepublic.com
Amazon book descriptions and book
reviews huge Facebook groups Google
answerthepublic.com and Google together
YouTube videos
and a tool called jasper.ai jasper.ai is
an artificial intelligence copywriting
app that helps you come up with the
words that your prospects need it allows
you to connect with what the prospects
desires are and it allows you to
actually understand and get into the
psychographics of what your prospect
really cares about it allows you to get
into the psychological framework of what
your prospect really wants from you
you're able to ask Jasper okay what is
the biggest fears of somebody that's
wanting to do this what's their deepest
desire and then it'll create sales copy
and messaging for you that's written in
a way
that persuades people to take action
with you
when you learn to build out offers that
connect with people that get them to
take action that persuade them to take
action that repel the wrong prospects
and attract the right ones when you
learn to do this it's very simple to do
I walk you through how to do this in my
client growth accelerator in my
copywriting Mastery course in the
virtual event Playbook course when you
learn how to do this it becomes
effortless for you to attract the right
leads and close sales and to get people
to buy from you and again the truth is
you're going to only have a limited
percentage of people actually ever
purchase anything from you that's
that's part of the process
and so don't beat yourself up because
you're not making thousands of sales
right away it takes time to build up to
that point as you dial in your messaging
and you're going to be constantly
dialing in that messaging getting it
more strategic getting your cost for per
lead down getting your sales conversions
up the more you communicate the more you
connect with your targeted Prospect the
more you actually do more virtual events
the better you're going to get with
actually connecting with people and so
that's why we highly recommend launching
a virtual event doing a virtual event
I'm using virtual events right now and
all of our stuff if you look at my
website jeremykurkowski.com I'm
promoting some kind of a virtual event
on there whether it be a one day event
or a five-day event we got an upcoming
five-day event here going on we've been
doing a couple of one day events that
then lead people to that five-day event
the goal with this is to connect with
people get them on my email list and
then when I open the doors to my
coaching program again these people are
already qualified they're already
wanting what we're throwing down and
they're ready to take action if you're a
coach if you're a trainer and you're a
mentor and you're not running virtual
events right now you're completely
messing at the process of what it's
actually going to bring in prospects for
you what you need to create offers that
entice people to give you the name and
email address you need to create offers
that get people to sign up with you so
that then you can make a sales
presentation to them you need to be
making sales presentations on a regular
basis if any piece of content that you
put out there did not lead to new sales
or New Leads it wasn't a good piece of
content likes follows shares
comments you name it those are worthless
they don't mean anything engagement
doesn't mean anything anymore it did
back in 2014 it doesn't anymore what
matters the most is are you capturing
people's information getting them on
your email list and then selling to
those people what you're offering on a
weekly basis
on a weekly basis on a regular
consistent basis week after week after
week after week because here's the thing
your competition is
successful coaches are if you're not
showing up week after week after week
doing this you're not going to look like
a serious business owner to your
prospects okay and so this isn't about
putting out a whole bunch of social
media content
it's about having an offer where people
can sign up with their name and email
address
for a certain date and time to show up
in front of you on camera on Zoom to
listen to you to present and to give
them practical skill sets that they can
apply to get a result and get a
transformation right away from that
training and then you have an
opportunity to make an Ask make an ask
to get them to buy from you and this is
the number one activity that coaches
trainers mentors and course creators
need to focus on right now is
consistently doing this over and over
and over again not just once in a blue
moon
not just once a month even
multiple times if you can as you start
doing this it's going to good on
autopilot for you it's going to become
very easy for you to just copy and paste
duplicate your last virtual event change
a few of the words maybe change the
graphic out and then relaunch it again
to a new group of people and that's what
we're doing is we're just basically
recycling the same events over and over
again tweaking them just slightly based
off of the feedback that we get from
people and here's the biggest ticker you
want to have a feedback loop you want to
have some way where people give you
feedback about what they want what they
want to learn what their struggles are
what their problems what their
frustrations are so then you can build
future offers and future virtual Events
off of what your actual Target customer
wants when you give your Target customer
what they want not what you want them to
want hear me out here
what you want to give people
what you want them to want
is not what you should be offering as
your offer just because it's going to
help somebody get that out of your brain
you want to give people what they want
what is the outcome that they want even
if it's not how what you normally would
do
even if it's not what you think is even
healthy for them even it's not what you
think is even helpful for them
what do they want give that to your
prospect
and you'll close a ton of sales
and what that then you deliver is so in
your offer in your offer copy and your
messaging it's based around what they
want and then you deliver what's going
to bring the transformation to people
which is what they both want and what
they need
so you're going to deliver to people
what they need
you're still going to have a high level
of Integrity in what you deliver you're
not going to just give people what they
want even though it's not going to help
them you're going to give them what they
want but also what they need that's
going to take them to the next level
you're going to reframe their beliefs
you're going to help them learn things
that they don't know yet about what you
offer you're going to reframe and shape
their belief systems but nobody cares
about anything you know I don't I mean
this politely how smart you are and all
the stuff you know and all the stuff
that you know how to help people do
doesn't matter if you don't give people
what they want
it doesn't because you're never going to
have an opportunity to give them what
they need until you give people what
they want
nobody cares how much you know until
they know how much you care and if
you're coming from a selfish place of
just trying to force feed people down
their throats what you think is going to
give them help what's going to help them
you're missing connecting with real
human beings it's not you know how human
beings connect okay
and so when you actually learn to
connect with what does your prospect
want even if it's harmful for them
even if it's not going to help them in
the long run giving them what they want
is going to attract the right Prospect
so then you can lead them to what they
need as part of your ecosystem and in
your virtual events that's the best
angle the best framework to use for
creating your virtual events all right
everybody you got to be doing virtual
events you got to be getting out there
you got to have set a time where you can
get in front of people and communicate
and connect with them and your business
will grow listen if this has helped you
share it with somebody
if you're not in the client growth
accelerator join the waiting list I
can't wait to see you in there Join one
of the virtual events that we're doing
see how I do virtual events learn the
process from me of what's working right
now to generate six and seven figures in
a coaching course business we'll talk
soon everybody have a good one